本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 闲鱼 黑色风车 魔法莉露姆
校对： 闲鱼  后期： 小安
冰块 我需要更多的冰块
Ice! I need more ice!
马上来
Comin' up.
克里斯 伙计
Chris, buddy.
我需要帮忙 感觉不太好
I need help man. I don't feel good.
我在唐人街的什么地方 一个小巷子里
I'm in Chinatown somewhere, some alleyway.
来接我 行吗
I need you to come pick me up.
卧底游戏 第一季 第八集
我们应该再睡一会儿 你说呢?
We should probably get some sleep, don't you think?
是的 我们是应该多睡一会儿
Yeah, we should probably get on that.
怎么了?
What?
这么说我算哪一个?
So which is it?
是你男朋友还是
Am I your boyfriend, or
那个什么 你知道的
is this just... you know.
我们在认真的谈这事吗?
Are we having "the talk"?
我只是说说
I'm just saying.
是的 你说的对 我是说
Yeah, you're right, I mean...
我们在同一个部门
We're in the same unit.
这事违反规定
It's against the rules.
不能这样了
It has to stop.
今晚是最后一次了 再也没有了
Tonight's the last time. Ever.
你真能装啊
You're so full of it.
杰西 我们不能告诉任何人
We can't tell anyone, Jesse.
莫兰德 丽贝卡
Moreland, Rebecca.
好的
Yeah.
说定了
Done.
我们说谎技术一流 对吧?
We're good liars, right?
我们要做的就是说谎
So all we have to do is lie.
本・垂德 二十一岁
Ben Trinder. Twenty-one years old.
法医做了毒理分析
Coroner did a tox screen.
GHB 又称液体迷魂药或G毒 是一种无色无味无臭的液体
GHB成阳性 注意了是 液体尼古丁
He was positive for GHB and get this: liquid nicotine.
真的假的?
Seriously?
这东西是致命的
That stuff's lethal.
GHB是一种派对毒品
GHB is a party drug.
技术含量低 小作坊就能做出来
It's low-tech, made in basement labs.
缉毒组认为毒贩子
Drug Squad's best guess is dealers
在里面加了尼古丁来提高兴奋度
add in the nicotine to pump up the high.
那又怎么样 加多了 掺的多了点?
So what, they overshot, put in a little too much?
如果这批货有问题 那么麻烦就大了
If there's a bad batch of drugs out there, things can get real ugly.
奴佛卡因 一种麻醉剂
记得几年前有个毒贩子在可卡因里掺杂奴佛卡因
Remember a few years ago that dealer that was cutting coke with novocaine?
是的 死了八个 三十多个进了重症监护室
Yeah, eight people died and thirty more in I.C.U.
所以我们得快速行动 否则死的孩子越来越多
So we need to move fast, before we end up with more dead kids.
我们现在又什么线索?
So what we got?
没什么 一个地址 他死之前
Not much, a location.
去了一个叫斯戴姆的地方
Before he died, he went to a place called Stem.
是个非法营业的俱乐部
It's an illegal after hours club.
- 从没听说过 - 我去过
- Never heard of it.  - I've been there.
每隔几个月就换地方 避免被查
It moves around every few months to avoid getting busted.
口口相传 只招待获邀的客人
Word of mouth, invitation only.
这么说吧 约翰 基本上 如果你过了三十
See John, basically, if you're over thirty...
缉毒组不想进行突查 他们认为会打草惊蛇
Drug Squad doesn't want to do a raid, they think it will spook the dealer.
毒贩子会彻底消失 但是毒品却一直在市面上
He'll disappear into thin air, and the drugs stay out there.
所以他们把案子交给我们
So they're handing the case over to us.
斯戴姆的老板叫乔・凯恩
The owner of Stem is Joe Kane.
他因为袭击他人入狱两次
He's gone down twice for assault,
一次用破酒瓶子弄瞎一只眼
once with a broken bottle, took out someone's eye.
这家伙脾气很大
This guy's got a temper.
毫无疑问 他知道谁是毒贩子 是谁在卖毒品
Guaranteed, he's going to know who the dealers are and who's selling.
缉毒组给我们送过来的 一张邀请卡
Drug Squad sent this over, it's an invitation card.
我们用它进俱乐部
We use it to get by the doorman.
杰西 你三十以下 交给你了
Jesse, you're under thirty, you can take point.
看看你能否进去弄清楚谁是毒贩子
See if you can get inside and get an idea on this dealer.
好的
Cool.
要不我和他一起去?
Why don't I go with him?
我之前去过 我了解里面的情况
I've been there before, I know the scene.
你也想去做卧底?
You wanna go undercover?
他们成长的太快了
They grow up so fast.
嘿 我以前也参加过行动
Hey, I've done plays before.
都是小的 但是 是个好主意
Small ones. But, yeah, good idea,
让你去闯闯吧
Let's unleash you into the world.
俱乐部的入口在士巴丹拿街上的一个中餐馆里
The entrance to the club is in a Chinese restaurant on Spadina.
根据缉毒组的消息 你们穿过餐馆进入后厨
According to Drug Squad, you go through the restaurant into the kitchen.
后面有个楼梯 会带你到俱乐部
There's a stairway in back. It'll take you down to the club.
你们身上都有监听
You'll both be wired.
玛利亚和约翰掌控全局 他们就在楼上
Maria and John will run cover. They'll be right upstairs.
今晚是私人派对
Private party tonight.
不是吧?邀请卡不好用?
Seriously? This card doesn't work?
哥们 今晚不行
Not tonight, man.
向后转吧
Turn around.
这样呢? 这样行吗?
What about this? This help?
私人派对 哥们 对不起了
It's a private party, bro. Sorry.
怎么样才行呢?
What's it going to take?
不可能 好吗?
It's not happening, alright?
向后转吧 别浪费时间了
So turn around, stop wasting my time.
我想乔看到你
I don't think Joey
拒绝这么漂亮的女生一定不会开心的
would be very happy with you turning away pretty girls.
你认识乔 是吗?
You know Joe do you?
我过去常来
I used to go to these parties all the time.
哦是吗?
Oh yeah?
那每次乔在那些顶级的DJ台上挂的是什么?
So what does Joe hang on top of the DJ booth at every location?
哥们 她当时太High了 没注意
Dude she was high, she wasn't paying attention.
不 不 不 我知道
No, no, no, I got this.
是个标记
It was a... sign.
是个卷轴之类的
It's one of those scrolling...
不要停止爱
"Don't Stop Love."
我说对了吗?
Am I right?
完全正确
I'm totally right.
进来两位
I got two coming down.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
宝贝 不要停止爱
Don't stop the love, baby.
好了他们进去了
Okay they're in.
你真的认识那个家伙 乔 那个老板
Do you really know that guy, Joe the owner?
不认识 从来没见过
Nope. Never met him.
你们的工作就是找到毒贩子 就这么简单
Your job is to ID the dealer, that's it.
你们找到目标 和服务生 酒保 老板聊聊
You're looking to score. Talk to waiters, bartenders,
如果能见到老板的话
the owner if you see him.
小心点 任何人发觉你们是警察
Be careful. Anyone smells you're a cop,
毒贩子就溜了
the dealer will vanish.
给你们来点什么?
What can I get you?
啤酒 伏特加加苏打水
Beer and a vodka soda.
你后面
Behind you.
是乔吗?
Is that Joe?
我不知道  脸上没伤很难判断
I don't know. It's hard to tell without the bruises
我们走近看一下
Let's get a closer look.
知道吗 应该我一个人去
You know what, it should just be me.
不带你 我可以接近他
I can get closer to him without you.
稍等一下
Wait just a sec.
我会小心的
I'll be careful.
女朋友?
Girlfriend?
是的 不 有点复杂
Yeah. No, it's complicated.
你是个混蛋了
So you're a dick.
不是
No.
我想让她做我的女朋友 只是得让她知道
I want her to be my girlfriend, I just have to convince her.
好极了 我憎恨混蛋
Good, I hate dicks.
乔 嗨
Joe, hi.
我喜欢这个新地方
I love the new building.
你不认得我了 是吧?
You don't recognize me, do you?
真的吗?
Seriously?
你就是这么一个人 哈?
You're one of those guys, huh?
卡丽
Khali.
哦 卡丽
Khali, right.
怎么回事?
What's happening?
卡丽找到老板了
Khali's ID'd the owner.
想得美
Nice try.
放过我吧 我每天遇见很多美女
Give me a break, I meet a lot of beautiful women.
哦 没错 说的没错
Oh right, good save.
干杯
Cheers.
我想开派对应该找谁?
So who do I talk to if I want to party?
告诉我找谁帮我介绍一下就行
Just point me in the right direction and push.
她也太直接了
She's blunt as hell.
你想办派对
You want to party.
最简单的方法
The direct approach.
小美眉 每人告诉你要对毒品说不吗?
No one's ever told you to say no to drugs, little girl?
一次都没有
Not even once.
真希望我能帮助你 但是我做不到
Wish I could help you out, I just can't do that.
真的吗?
Really?
抱歉
Sorry.
你是个摄影师 对吗?
You're a photographer, right?
是的
Yeah.
那些是你照的吗?
Are those yours?
你喜欢?
You like?
你开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding?
我的大爱 他们太棒了
I love, they're amazing.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也是摄影师?
Are you a photographer?
我曾经很想
I always wanted to be.
也许你可以给我些建议
Maybe you could give me some pointers.
你想知道什么?
What would you like to know?
这是干嘛的?
What does this do?
要再来杯啤酒吗?
You want another beer?
能和我喝一杯吗?
Will you do a shot with me?
两杯伏特加 一杯给你
Two shots of vodka. One for you.
我叫杰西
I'm Jesse.
碧豆
Beetle.
什么?
What?
像那个虫子(指甲壳虫)
Like the bug.
这里一定有个家伙在出货 对吧?
There's gotta be a guy around here who's selling, right?
我想买点
I'm looking to score.
我想说的是希望你能帮我
Is what I'm saying, hoping you could help me.
我希望我能帮你 但是这家伙今晚不在
I wish I could, but our guy's not in tonight.
真的吗?
Really?
你看起来挺失望的
You look so disappointed.
杰西 谢谢请我喝酒
Thanks for the drink, Jesse.
- 我们走吧 - 好的
- Let's go.  - Aliright.
怎么?
What's going on?
乔也确定今晚毒贩子不在
Joe's confirmed the dealer's not in the house.
卡丽要和那家伙去什么地方吗?
Is Khali going somewhere with that guy?
我觉得有点不对头
I've got a bad feeling about this.
他楼上有公寓 他要给她看些照片
He's got an apartment upstairs, he's going to show her some photos.
我要你跟着他们 好吗? 我也不喜欢这样
I want you to stay with them, okay? I don't like it either.
但是我们能监听到
But we got ears.
我们让她继续
We're going to let this one play.
别把她弄丢了
Don't lose her.
我就在他们后面 他们要进后面了
I'm right behind them. They're going in back.
- 好的 盯着他们 好吗? - 好的
- All right. Stay with them, OK?  - Done.
这么做好吗?
Is this a good idea?
他们单独在一起她会获得更多的情报
She'll get more from him when they're alone,
如果运气好的话 毒贩子也许给他打个电话呢
then with a bit of luck, the dealer might make a house call.
你没事吧?
You okay?
我跟丢了 保镖不让我进去
I lost her. Bouncer won't let me through.
好的 那就赶快回到我这来
Alright, just get back up here fast.
嗯 地方有点乱 但是
Well, it's kind of mess but...
请进 请进 别拘束
come in, come in, make yourself at home.
哇喔 这地方真不错
Wow, this place is great.
她进去了
She's inside.
三楼 六号
Third floor, apartment six.
喝点酒 看点照片 我有惊喜给你
Have some drinks, look at some photos, then I have a surprise for you.
惊喜? 什么惊喜?
Surprise, what is it?
你会喜欢的
You're going to like it.
三楼有一个消防通道 我们快走
On the third floor there's a fire escape, let's go.
如果发生意外 你知道该怎么做
Anything bad happens, you know what to do.
我明白 你们快去吧
I got it, get up there, hurry.
我来让它从头播放 请便
Let me just pull this up. Be my guest.
哦哇 太令人惊讶了
Oh wow, these are amazing.
你是怎样抓拍到这些人的
Look at how you captured all those people.
我可是干这行的
That's what I do.
你在给我调什么饮料?
What are you pouring me?
大杯鸡尾酒
A big fat cocktail.
你想把我灌醉吗?
You trying to get me loaded or something?
那我就可以占你便宜了
Then I'm going to take advantage of you.
希望你能有这个运气
Good luck with that.
约翰 快点 情况有点不妙
John, hurry. I don't like what I'm hearing.
再加点这个...
A little of this...
好的 然后...
Alright, and...
完成了
Be right there...
你太有才了
You are so talented.
真是让我大开眼界
This is amazing.
谢谢
Thank you.
干杯
Cheers.
我有东西要送给你 一个小礼物
So, I have something for you. A little gift.
伸出手来
Hold out your hand.
这是了解一个人最好的方法
Best way to get to know someone.
喝了它你会兴奋到极点
You get high with them.
让你兴奋到忘乎所以
You get right 'under their skin'.
约翰 他正让她尝试毒品
John, he's offering her drugs.
她怎么样?
How is she?
她在拖延时间 但你要尽快赶过去
She's holding her own, but you gotta move.
你在哪得到这东西的? 你和交易商有联系?
Where do you get this stuff, you got a dealer?
别担心 喝了它就是了
Don't worry about it, just enjoy, alright.
我也想
I want to.
但总感觉抛开朋友自己享用不太好
I just feel so bad for ditching my friends like this.
你不能给他们打电话
You can't call.
你之前喝过GHB吗?
Have you ever had GHB before?
它成分非常纯净 很受欢迎
This stuff is very pure, very clean, it's very designer.
就像液体迷幻剂
Just like liquid E.
我朋友在楼下等我
My friends are going to want me downstairs.
再多待一会吧
Stay a little.
让我来帮你
Let me help you out here.
张开嘴 快张开嘴
Open your mouth, open your mouth.
很抱歉 我要走了
You know what I'm going to have to bail.
- 什么? 我不明白 - 多谢你的款待
- What I don't get it? - Thanks for the drink.
怎样才可以让你留下来?
How can I talk you into staying?
为什么你那么紧张? 我们只是一起喝点东西
Why are you freaking out on me? We're just having drinks.
- 嘿! - 形势越来越紧张了
- Hey! - Things are getting tense.
你在哪?
Where are you?
我们现在在顶层 门被锁住了
We're at the top. The door's locked!
嘿 放开我!
Hey, get off me!
为什么你要离开?
What makes you think you're going to leave?
她遇到麻烦了 快进去解救她
She's in trouble. Get in there, get her out.
放开我! 我要走了!
Get off me! I wanna go!
你不是想要派对吗?
You wanna party?
我们现在就开派对 小贱人
We're gonna party, you little bitch.
警察!
Police!
放开她!
Get off her!
卡丽?
Khali?
她没事
She's OK.
杰西 够了别打了
Jesse, that's enough.
你还好吗?
You OK?
他交给我了
I got him.
对 就在那
Right there, yeah.
他强迫我喝GHB
He was trying to get me to take GHB.
然后他把我推到墙角 我无处可逃
Then he slams me up against the wall. It came out of nowhere.
我没事 真的没事
But I'm fine, it's fine.
你看起来并不好 你的嘴唇破了
You're not fine. Your lips.
没关系
It's okay.
一点都不疼
It doesn't hurt.
总之你开车送她去医院
You're going to drive her to the hospital anyway,
做个检查
get it checked out.
你也知道 我们需要医检报告
We need the medical report, you know that.
- 我没事 - 别说了
- I'm fine. - Don't argue.
听着 在这种紧张的形势下
Look, this was a tough situation,
你已经做的很好了
you did good.
走吧
Come on.
怎么了?
What's going on?
刚收到的
This just came in.
泰勒・克拉克
Tyler Clarke.
二十岁 GHB里混有液态尼古丁
Twenty years old. GHB laced with liquid nicotine.
我们手里又多了一个服药过量的案子
We got another overdose on our hands.
我以为他要杀你
I thought he was going to kill you.
你和他在一起的时候
You were in there with him,
我却无法到你身边保护你
and I couldn't get to you.
嘿 我没事 没关系的
Hey. I'm okay. It's okay.
不 有关系! 刚才很危险
No it's not okay! That was brutal.
你差点在丽贝卡面前暴露我们的关系
You nearly blew our cover with Rebecca,
你知道吗?
you know.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你真的很难过
You're really upset.
你现在才看出来吗?
You just figured that out now?
我把血渍沾你嘴上了
I'm getting blood on you.
走吧 我来开车
C'mon on, I'll drive.
这是圈套 我是被陷害的
This is entrapment. I was set up.
是吗? 那事实怎样?
Yeah? How's that?
那些毒品不是我的 是她的
Those weren't my drugs, they were hers.
肯定是她把毒品带到我屋里去的
She must've brought them up to my place,
这是常有的事
happens all the time.
我没有碰她
I didn't touch her,
是她先袭击我的
she attacked me,
我是在正当防卫
I was defending myself.
- 乔. - 信她还是信我
- Joe. - It's her word against mine.
谁知道呢 或许你足够走运
Who knows, maybe you'll get lucky.
法官会相信你说的话
Maybe the judge'll believe you.
但现在 我才不关心呢
At this moment, I couldn't care less.
本・垂德, 泰勒・克拉克.
Ben Trinder, Taylor Clarke.
这两个男孩都在你的俱乐部里买了毒品
Both of these kids bought drugs at your club.
GHB 你应该知道的比我多
GHB, you know all about it.
我们在你厨房里找到了一打
We found a dozen caps in your kitchen.
就是这些毒品杀害了他们 他们才刚刚二十岁
It killed them. These kids were barely twenty.
或许他们是从别处买的
Maybe they got them somewhere else,
肯定是的 因为我的俱乐部里不卖毒品
All right, cause I don't allow drugs in my club.
这是违法的
That would be illegal...
我现在没有心情和你玩...
I'm not in the mood to play games...
我才不在乎你有没有心情呢 女士!
I don't care what the hell you're in the mood for, lady!
你把我带到这里 想栽赃给我
You drag me down here, you throw all this crap at me.
如果这些毒品被人买走...
If anymore of these drugs get sold...
那不关我的事!
That's not my problem!
我没有做错任何事!
I have done nothing wrong!
现在我可以打个电话吗?
Now can I please make my phone call?
我们没法控告乔・凯恩 但是我们暂时
We got nothing from Joe Kane, but we're holding him,
以伤害罪和非法经营酒吧罪扣留他
for assault and running an illegal bar.
又一起服药过量案件和俱乐部有关 死因相同
A second OD has been linked back to the club. Same cause of death.
我应该提醒你们 上面给了我很大的压力
I should warn you. I'm getting big pressure from the brass.
他们想关停俱乐部
They want to shut the club down.
这不是个好主意 他们会换个地方的
That's a bad idea, it'll just pop up somewhere else.
他们要求我们在二十四小时内破案
They're giving us 24 hours to get this done.
什么? 你在开玩笑吗?
What? You're kidding me.
你想给我们展示那晚你的成果吗?
You wanna show us the spoils of your evening?
我从乔的笔记本上拷了一千张照片
I grabbed over a 1,000 photos from Joe's laptop.
这是其中十五张 拍自十五个不同的晚上
So far, fifteen of them, from fifteen different nights.
这个家伙 总是出现
This guy, he's in the background.
站在一个特定的地方 然后有人去找他
Standing in one spot and people coming up to him.
看起来像在做交易
That looks like a buy
我要是能看到他们的手就好了
if I could see their hands.
我们需要知道他是谁 从乔那里
We need a name, that's going to come from our friend Joe.
还有调酒师碧豆
The bartender, Beetle.
你找到突破点了?
You got an angle?
她喜欢英俊的小伙子
She likes nice guys.
我想我可以去扮伤心要同情
I'm thinking I could be a little heart broken.
这是目前最好的办法了
That's our best move.
好的 那我马上回俱乐部
Okay, so I'll head back into the club.
不用了 今晚你退出行动
Not you. You got the night off.
我们也应该在街上增派人员
We should also be working the street.
联系你们的线人也许他们有线索
Check with your CI's maybe they've heard something.
我们必须马上抓到这个毒贩子
We need to get this dealer now.
卡丽 有时间吗?
Khali, got a second?
能把门关上吗?
Can you shut the door?
你脸怎么样?
How's your face?
有点疼
It's hurting.
假如
Hypothetical.
我的两个探员私下里交往过密
If two of my officers were becoming personally involved,
对我来说可能是个麻烦
it would be a problem for me.
我不得不按程序处理
I'd have to follow procedure.
把其中一个从这里调出去
Transfer one of them out of the unit.
如果这真的发生的话
If they were.
是的
Yeah.
一旦牵扯到感情 你不能清晰的思考
That kind of emotion, you can't think clearly.
卡丽 这不是游戏 孩子们正在被杀害
This isn't a game Khali, kids are dying.
你做出错误的选择 或一旦分心
You make bad choices, you get distracted.
大家的性命都会有危险
You put everyone's life in danger.
我不想看到这样的事情发生
I wouldn't want that to happen.
我也是
Me either.
我还需要和其他人进行这样的谈话吗?
Do I need to have this talk with anyone else?
不 你说得很对
No, you're good.
我做过很多疯狂又愚蠢的事去引起她的注意
I've done some crazy-ass things to impress her.
昨晚和你在一起的那个女孩吗?
This is the girl from last night?
记得有一次在高中...
This one time in high school...
这真的有点难以启齿
this is kinda embarrassing.
你做了很愚蠢的事情
You did something stupid.
我想向她展示我多么敏捷就从窗台跳了下去
I wanted to show her how agile I was so I jumped out of a window
结果摔断了腿
and I broke my leg.
但这奏效了 非常成功
But it worked, big time.
所以你对她真的很好 哈
So you're sweet, huh.
你就是这么和她上床的 凡事都顺着她?
That's how you get laid, by being a sweetheart?
或许我应该尝试硬气一些
Should try being hardcore,
看看女孩子是否更喜欢那样?
see if girls like that better?
不 不 继续对她好 体贴人是件好事
No, no, stick with sweet, sweet is good.
她今晚在哪呢 你的灵魂伴侣?
So where is she tonight, your soulmate?
不知道 或许她背着我出去和别的男人鬼混了
I don't know, she's probably out cheating on me.
你笑什么 很好笑吗?
What, that's funny?
她也许正和吉他手滚床单呢
She's banging some guitar player.
他给她写了首歌
This guy wrote a song for her.
我还能怎么做?
How am I suppose to compete with that?
那就做点比这还甜蜜的事
You got out-sweeted.
今晚我要让自己玩到疯
The way this night is going, I need to get high.
喝个酩酊大醉
I need to get completely messed up.
我本不该这样做的
I should not be doing this.
跟他提我
Mention my name,
他会帮你拿货的 好吧
and he will hook you up, okay.
我走了 你对我真好
Off I go. You're the best.
记住 小心点
Watch yourself, okay?
利亚姆这人有点疯狂
Liam's a little crazy.
在他那凡事都小心点
No sudden moves around him.
来人啊! 这需要帮助!
Help! We need help in here!
这个家伙没有呼吸了!
This guy isn't breathing!
我不知道 他刚刚在我面前昏倒了
I don't know. He just keeled over, right in front of me.
你能讲话吗?
Can you talk?
叫救护车了吗?
Did you call an ambulance?
叫了 我再打一次 问他们多久能到
Yeah, I'll call back and see how far they are.
马克!
Mark!
他怎么了!?
What happened to him!?
你认识他?
You know this guy?
他喝了什么? 谁给他的?
What did he take? Who gave it to him?
我不知道 我看到他时他就躺在地上了
I don't know, he was lying on the ground.
马克 快醒醒! 噢 天哪
Mark, wake up! Oh God,
他究竟喝了什么?
what did he take?
我需要帮忙 突发事件 在男洗手间 现在!
I need help, emergency, in the men's washroom, now!
这个男孩叫马克・卡梅伦
His name is Mark Cameron.
在送达西奈医院时死亡
He was DOA at Mount Sinai.
第三起服药过量死亡案件
Three OD's.
三个不同的夜晚
Three different nights.
都是从一个俱乐部里出来的
All from the same club.
保镖似乎没想过出这样的事
The bouncer seemed to really take it hard.
看看这个 这是马克的手机
Take a look at this, it's Mark's phone.
那是另外两个受害者
That's the other two victims.
也就是说他们三个都互相认识
So they knew each other, all three of them?
他们都是朋友
They were all friends?
他们一起狂欢 从同一个毒贩那买货
They partied together, had the same dealer?
估计是利亚姆
Presumably Liam.
好吧 但等等
Okay, but wait.
他死的那晚马克收到了一条短信
The night he died, Mark got a text.
"嘿宝贝 你今晚真应该到斯戴姆来
"Hey, baby, you should come to Stem tonight,
我在狂欢 等不及要见你了"
I'm partying, dying to meet you."
来自一次性手机 不可能追踪得到
Came from a burner cell, it's impossible to trace.
再看看本的手机 两天之前
And check out Ben's phone, two nights earlier.
完全相同的短信
Same text word for word.
他们是被引诱到那个俱乐部的
They were lured to the club.
有人盯上了这几个孩子 一个接着一个
Someone is targeting these boys, one by one.
我们面对的是多起谋杀
We're dealing with multiple murders.
好了 丹尼 我们要找到利亚姆
OK, Danny, we need to find Liam
然后做成一次交易
and make a buy.
我们需要把他逮捕进来问话
We need to bring him in for questioning.
没问题 我现在在三楼
You got it. I'm on the third floor now.
把你看到的告诉我
Tell me what you see.
看起来是一个血汗工厂
Looks like a sweatshop,
一定是在后面
must be at the back.
注意安全 碧豆说他是个疯子
Be careful, Beetle said he's crazy.
那么这应该会很有趣咯
So this should be fun then?
嘿 我要找利亚姆
Hey, I'm looking for Liam.
缉毒警察在找那些男孩的家人了解情况
Drug Squad's following up with the families of the boys.
或许他们了解一些事情
Maybe they know something.
本・垂德有案底
Ben Trinder has a sheet.
意图贩毒 两次被抓
Possession for the purpose, two counts.
也就是说 这些家伙在做贩毒生意
So what, these guys are in the drug business?
在利亚姆的地盘上
Honing in on Liam's turf
他不喜欢竞争对手 于是决定除掉他们
and he didn't like the competition, and decided to take them out?
有可能 或许是个动机
It's possible. Could be a motive.
嘿 我是丹尼尔 我就是打电话的那个
Hey, I'm Daniel. I'm the one that called.
郊区来的丹尼尔 你好吗
Daniel from the suburbs, how you doing?
我不玩了
I'm out.
来这边 我们在这里聊聊
Come over here, let's talk over here.
听着...
Listen...
我听说你或许可以帮帮我
I heard you could help me out, maybe.
你听说的 是吗
You heard that, huh?
我不会让你浪费时间的 哥们
I could make it worth your while, man.
你现在有的我全要了
I'll take everything you got right now.
你是想聊聊 还是我可以走人了
You want to talk about it or should I turn around?
你是乔的一个朋友
You're a friend of Joe's?
对
Yeah.
我喜欢乔 他是个正直的家伙
I like Joe. He's a stand-up guy.
是吗 我听说他是个混蛋
Really? I think he's a dick.
这家伙是个喜剧演员
This guy's a comedian.
我能给你看样东西吗
Can I show you something?
瞧瞧这个 我刚刚拿到手的
Look at this, I just got this,
好像有四百年历史了
it's like four hundred years old.
你是个警察吗 丹尼尔
Are you a cop, Daniel?
因为如果你是的话
'Cause if you are,
我会用我的古董刀把你开肠破肚的
I'm going to gut you with my antique knife.
插进去就像切黄油一样 它就是这么锋利
Goes in like butter, that's how sharp it is.
我知道的
I know.
我已经试过了
I already tried it,
在上一个想成为我朋友的警察身上
on the last cop who wanted to be my friend.
放松点 好吗
Let's relax, alright?
如果我是一个警察 你早就被逮捕了
If I was a cop, you'd be in cuffs right now.
你害怕了
You're scared.
哦天啊 你害怕了
Oh boy, you're scared.
你在干什么 兄弟
What are you doing, man?
你要在我的衬衫上弄出一个洞吗
Are you putting a hole in my shirt?
你知道这件衬衫多贵吗
You know how much this shirt cost?
哦天呐 我把它弄坏了
Oh man, I wrecked it.
听着 乔说你的货很好 我要买一批
Look, Joe said you had good stuff, and I'm buying in bulk.
如果你觉得我是一个警察
So if you think I'm a cop,
我还是去找别人买货好了
then I'll go buy my stuff somewhere else.
找一个不那么疑神疑鬼的人
From someone less paranoid, maybe.
你说的"一批"
What's that mean:
是什么意思
"bulk".
两升起步
Two liters to start?
好了 卡丽 你发现了什么
OK, Khali, what have you got?
实验室报告
Lab reports.
血液和马克・卡梅伦的匹配
The blood work from Mark Cameron is a match.
这三个男孩的死因相同
All three boys died of the same thing.
同种的GHB
Same bunch of GHB.
和疯子利亚姆卖给丹尼尔的完全相同
It's identical and matches what Crazy Liam sold to Daniel.
除了一样东西
Except for one thing.
尼古丁
The nicotine.
对 丹尼尔买到的没有被掺东西 它是纯净的
Yeah. What Daniel bought wasn't laced, it was clean.
所以利亚姆只给几个胶囊掺了东西
So Liam was lacing the individual caps.
有目标的杀戮 他想除掉竞争对手
Targeted killings. He wanted to take out his competition.
我们应该和保镖谈谈 奥兰多
We should talk to the bouncer, Orlando.
当马克躺在地上的时候 他的反应
When Mark was on the floor there, his reaction?
我觉得他认识他们
I think he knows them.
如果这些男孩想接管利亚姆的生意
Makes sense if these boys want to
这也说得通
take over Liam's business.
奥兰多在那里工作 他或许有牵连
Orlando worked there, he could be involved.
我要去拜访他一下
I'm going to go pay him a visit.
看看他能不能帮我解答些问题
See if he can fill in some blanks.
你想不想去利亚姆那里
You wanna have a go at Liam there?
好的
Yeah.
不
No.
我不想见你 我想要那个坑了我的警察
I don't want you, I want the cop that tricked me.
你为何不出去把他叫进来
Why don't you go out there and get him and bring him back
因为我有些事情要给他说
cause I got a couple of things I want to say to him.
你说够了吗
You finished?
因为我有些坏消息 利亚姆
'Cause I got some bad news for you, Liam.
贩毒已经足够糟了 再加上杀人
Trafficking was bad enough, but now manslaughter.
你完蛋了
You're screwed.
你在说些什么
What the hell are you talking about?
那些你在斯戴姆卖的GHB胶囊
Those GHB caps you're selling at the Stem,
你给它们下了毒
you've been cutting them with poison.
液态尼古丁
Liquid nicotine.
我没有
No, I'm not.
你有的
Oh yes, you are.
三个死掉的孩子 利亚姆 那可不妙啊
Three dead kids, Liam, that's not good.
喂 别说了
Whoa, whoa, just stop!
你好好想一想
Just think about it for a second.
首先 我是一个艺术家 好吗
A, I'm an artist, alright,
我对我的作品很骄傲
I take pride in my work.
其次 我怎么会杀掉我的客户呢
B, I'd be killing off my own clientele.
开玩笑吧 你觉得我会想让自己失业
What? You think I'm trying to put myself out of business?
我不知道 或许你想让别人失业
I don't know, maybe you're trying to put them out of business.
你在说些什么
What are you talking about?
那些孩子是不是闯进你的地盘了 利亚姆
Were those kids stepping on your turf, Liam?
听着 这件事可能是我任何一个客户干的
Look. Any one of my customers could have done it.
好好算算吧 那个俱乐部里有数百个孩子
Do the math, hundreds of kids in that club.
利亚姆那么你告诉我 是谁干的?
Then you tell me, which one did it Liam?
给我找律师 就现在
My lawyer, right now,
在此之前我一句话都不会说
before I say another word.
给这个家伙找个律师
Let's get this kid a lawyer.
他会需要的
He's going to need one.
早上好 奥兰多
Good morning, Orlando.
警探 丽贝卡・爱丽丝
Rebecca Ellis, Detective Sergeant.
我有几个问题要问你
I have a couple of questions for you.
关于什么的
About what?
你的朋友 马克
Your friend, Mark.
他在医院去世了 我很抱歉
He died at the hospital. I'm sorry.
好的... 请进
Yeah... come in.
你现在住在乔的家里了
So you're crashing at Joe's place?
对 他被逮捕了 我帮他照看一下家
Yeah, he got arrested. I'm looking after it for him.
你怎么知道我在这里
How'd you know I was here?
就是我逮捕的他
I'm the one who arrested him.
你是否也认识这两个孩子
Did you know these two boys as well?
泰勒・克拉克还有本・垂德
Tyler Clarke and Ben Trinder.
不
No.
我是说 他们是来过俱乐部 他们服药过量了
I mean, yeah they came to the club. They OD'd.
我就知道这些
That's all I know.
谁给的他们GHB
Who gave them the GHB?
谁想让他们死 奥兰多
Who wants them dead Orlando?
或许他们在贩毒 惹毛了某人
They were dealing drugs maybe? Pissed someone off?
得了吧 你在俱乐部工作
C'mon you work at the club,
你能注意到很多事情
you see things.
我说了...
Like I said...
他们来俱乐部 他们喜欢在俱乐部闲逛
They come to the club, they like to hang out at the club.
我们很友好 仅此而已
We're friendly, that's it.
还有吗
And what else?
没了
Nothing.
奥兰多 你一定知道点什么
Orlando, you know something about this.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what happened.
你告诉我会感觉好些的
You'll feel better when you do.
我不会的 相信我
No I won't, believe me.
我没办法不想这件事情
I can't stop thinking about it.
你看到了什么
What did you see?
不好的事情
Something bad.
非常非常不好的事情
Something very, very bad.
在俱乐部里的后面 有一个储藏室
There's this stock room, in the club, in the back.
那里有一个女孩
And there's a girl.
哥们 你来不来
Bro, you in or out?
那是本 那个死掉的家伙 那个服药过量的
It was Ben, the guy that died, that OD'd.
本・垂德
Ben Trinder?
对 马克也在那里
Yeah. And Mark was there too.
他们在脱她的衣服
They were taking off her clothes.
她是谁
Who is she?
我不知道 某个女孩 叫做萨蒂
I don't know, man, some girl, named Sadie.
你到底来不来
So you in or out?
然后我什么也没做
And I did nothing.
我去了酒吧
I went to the bar.
喝了几杯 磕了药
I got shots, I got wasted.
我看到那个女孩出来了 萨蒂
I saw the girl come out, Sadie.
她看起来很糟 她在哭
She looked bad, she was crying.
我不知道她是谁
I don't know who she was,
我以前从来没在酒吧看到过她
I never saw her at the bar before.
我本应该做些什么 我本应该
I should've done something, I should have.
我为什么没有报警
I should have... why didn't I call the cops?
我为什么没进去亲自阻止他们
Why didn't I go in there, myself?
那个房间里有多少人和萨蒂在一起
How many guys were in the room with Sadie?
五个... 五个
Five... five.
马克 泰勒 本 还有另外两个
Mark, Tyler, Ben, and two more.
我不认识他们
I don't know them.
奥兰多 有人盯上了这些男孩
Orlando, someone's targeting these boys.
如果还有那两个人...
If there's two out there...
我很抱歉 我不知道他们的名字
I'm sorry, I don't know their names.
听着 我说的是实话
Look, I'm telling you the truth.
萨蒂什么
Sadie what?
没有姓
No last name.
找出上个月的性侵犯列表
Just pull up sexual assaults in the last month.
没有结果 她可能没有报案
Nothing. She probably didn't report it.
做一个一般检索 女孩 十六到二十四岁
Do a general search. Girls, 16 to 24,
名字开头字母是"S"
first name starts with "S"...
好吧 看来有五百个结果
Okay. There's like five hundred.
什么
What?
萨蒂・杰森
Sadie Jansen.
哦 天呐 她两周前自杀了
Oh God, she committed suicide two weeks ago.
上吊自杀
Hanged herself.
谁报的警 上面写了吗
Who called it in? Does it say?
她的父母出城了 发现她的是...
Her parents were out of town, she was found by...
什么
What?
她的姐姐 布林内・杰森
Her sister. Brynne Jansen.
昵称 碧豆
Nickname, Beetle.
她把强奸她妹妹的男孩作为目标
She's targeting the boys who raped her sister.
所以她买了药 加上尼古丁
So she buys the drugs, adds the nicotine,
把他们勾引到俱乐部里 在他们的饮料里投毒
lures them into the club, spikes their drinks.
让那看起来像是服药过量
Makes it look like an OD.
所以这是十足的复仇
So it's revenge, pure and simple.
她还有两个目标
And she has two more targets out there.
她可能在任何时候毒死他们
She could poison them any minute.
- 我们知道名字了吗 - 暂时还不知道
- We got names? - We're not there yet.
为什么我们不能带她过来
Why don't we just pick her up?
你有没有和凶杀组交流
Have you talked to Homicide?
她不在家 也不接电话
She's not at home, she's not answering her phone.
而且我们目前还没有足够的证据
Besides, we don't have enough evidence, not yet.
杰西你今晚还去俱乐部 你和卡丽两个
Jesse you're going to the club tonight, you and Khali.
我们需要供词 可以吗? 好了 我们行动吧
We need to get a confession. Okay? All right, let's get this done.
今晚需要所有人都参加行动
It's going to be all hands on deck tonight,
包括卡丽 都仔细听
including Khali, everyone has ears.
杰西是主角
Jesse will take point.
约翰和丹尼尔在楼上的餐厅做后援
John and Daniel will be upstairs in the restaurant for back up.
玛利亚和我在车里
Maria and I will be in the van.
我们一切就绪 有声音了
We're good, we got audio.
她不在吧台
She's not at the bar.
你能在这稍等我一下吗?
You wanna hang back for a second?
我找碧豆
I'm looking for Beetle.
我也在找
You and me both.
她今晚不上班?
She's not working tonight?
找到她 告诉她快过来 我需要帮手
When you find her, tell her to get back here, I need help.
她在这里
She's here somewhere.
她不见了
She's gone AWOL.
好吧 我们四周看看
Okay, let's take a look around.
卡丽 你需要检查整个俱乐部
Khali, you need to search the entire club.
奥兰多说过一个储藏室 看看你能不能找到
Orlando mentioned a stock room, see if you can find it.
没看到她 我们分开行动
No sign of her yet, we're going to split up.
我找到她了
I found her.
碧豆在储藏室
Beetle's in the stock room.
她在干嘛?
What's she doing?
坐在那 地板上
Sitting there, on the ground.
看起来很紧张
She's looking pretty rattled.
我一直在想
I just keep thinking.
如果我关心的人被伤害 如果我能想象的出
If somebody I care about got hurt, if I could picture that.
我是什么感觉
How I'd feel.
好的 杰西 好好利用 尽量拿到一份证词
That's good, Jesse, use it, try and get a confession.
你有五分钟时间 如果没结果
You've got five minutes, if it doesn't work,
我们就靠目前手上的证据逮捕她
we arrest her on the evidence we have.
证据不是充分 所以你要尽力
Which isn't much, so give me your best shot.
我就在外面
I'll be right outside.
哦 对不起 我不知道你在这
Oh sorry, I didn't know you were in here.
你在干吗呢?
What are you doing?
我刚碰到我的前女友 那天晚上跟你说的那个
I just ran into my ex again. From that night, I told you?
她又和那个家伙在一起了
She was with that guy, again.
那个吉他手
The guitar player.
对不起 我就是需要点时间
Sorry, I just... I need a second.
你不能待在这 快走吧
You can't stay here, you should go.
我需要喝一杯 你要来一杯吗?
I just need a drink. You wanna do a shot?
说实话 看样子你也需要喝一杯
To tell you the truth, you look like you could use one.
对不起 我不该管闲事
Sorry, it's not my business.
和卡丽的那个家伙 不是好东西
That guy with Khali, he's bad news.
我看的出来
I can tell.
我脑子里一直在想
I keep getting these pictures in my head.
如果他伤了她
If he ever hurt her...
我会疯掉的
I'd go crazy.
你会发疯的
You'd get mad.
还用说吗
Hell yeah.
能有多疯狂?
How mad?
说实话吗? 如果他真伤了她?
Honestly? If he hurt her bad?
以我对她的感情
The way I feel about her.
我真看不出我还能保持冷静
I don't see how I wouldn't lose control.
那时你已经无法思考
You wouldn't be able to think,
甚至连呼吸都不行
or breathe.
没错
Exactly.
你完全被怒火控制
It would take you over.
看起来你有过相似的经历啊
Sounds like you've been there before.
是的 你怎么这么说?
Yeah. What makes you say that?
因为我以前也经历过
Because I've been there before.
真的 我做过一些坏事
It's true. I've done some bad things.
碧豆 发生了什么事? 你也做过吗?
What happened, Beetle? Did you do something?
我妹妹
My little sister.
一群禽兽把她灌醉了 给她嗑药 然后
A bunch of guys got her drunk and high and...
他们伤害了她
they hurt her.
是吗? 有多糟?
Yeah? How bad?
他们强奸了她
They raped her.
就在这 在这个屋子里
Right here, right in this room.
我每天醒来都在想
And I wake up every day thinking,
我要让这些家伙都死光
all I want is for those guys to be dead.
好了开始了
Alright here we go.
但是你个子不高
But you're not that big, though.
也没有必要
You don't have to be.
你怎么做的?
How would you do it?
毒药的妙处在于 他们都不知道自己是怎么了
The thing about poison is, they don't know what's happening to them.
你不用告诉他们你为什么要杀他们
You don't get to tell them why you're killing them.
但是这最后的一个家伙
But this last guy,
我告诉他了
I told him.
我说你强奸了莎蒂
I said "You raped Sadie"
他哭着求我
And he begged and cried.
是谁?
Who did?
谁哭着求你?
Who begged and cried?
你做了什么?
Did you do something?
他在哪?
Where is he?
我本不应该告诉你的
I shouldn't have told you.
碧豆 他在哪?
Beetle, where is he?
他在那吗?
Is he in there?
别过来 别过来
Stay back, stay back!
把枪放下 别激动
Put it down. Take it easy.
约翰 快进去 她手里有枪
John, get in there. There's weapon in play.
哦天啊
Oh, God.
卡丽 原地待命
Khali, stay where you are.
我会开枪的 我要让他死
I will shoot you. I want him dead.
放下枪
Put it down.
他必须死在那
He stays in there until he's dead!
退回去 待在原地别动
Get back, stay right where you are!
卡丽 卡丽
Khali! Khali!
碧豆
Beetle.
碧豆 你不认识我
Beetle, You don't know me.
碧豆 我是警察
I'm a cop, Beetle.
杰西也是 我们是卧底警察
So is Jesse. We're undercover cops.
卡丽 离开这 快点 出去
Khali, out of here, go, get out.
外面还有警察吗?
Are there more cops outside?
Are there more cops outside?!
是的 是的外面有
Yes, yes there are.
碧豆 求你把枪放下
Beetle, please just put down the gun.
如果他们进来 我就杀了他
If they come in here, I will shoot him.
我才不管别的 我要杀了他 你告诉他们
I don't care, I will kill him. You tell them that.
- 好的 好的 - 我不在乎
- Okay, okay. - I don't care.
好的 我会告诉他们
OK, I'll let them know.
听我说
Listen to me.
我知道你妹妹被伤害
I know that your sister got hurt.
那些家伙用最卑鄙的方法伤害了她
That those boys hurt her in the worst way,
她最后也自杀了
and that she took her life.
你是在劝我放弃或者别的什么吗?
Are you trying to talk me down now or something?
你在开玩笑呢?
You kidding me?
我是应该这么做 但我从来没做过
That's what I'm supposed to do, but I've never done this before, so...
闭嘴
Shut up!
好的 好的 好的 好的
OK, OK, alright, alright. Alright.
约翰 情况紧急 你快到了吗?
John, it's escalating, are you close?
快了
Almost there.
出去 快啊
Get out! Go!
听我说 好吗?
Just listen to me, okay?
我进来 不是因为我是警察
I came in here not because I'm a cop,
是因为我
but because I...
我爱他
I love him.
我爱他 没有人知道
I'm in love with him and no one knows.
我的同事不知道 甚至连他都不知道
None of the people we work with, not even him.
所以如果你 如果你伤了他
So if you... if you hurt him,
我会和你现在的处境一样
I'll be exactly, where you are right now,
我爱的人死了 没了
with the person I love dead and gone.
我会和你一样痛苦的无法自拔
And I'll be in all the pain you're in.
所以我求你了
So I'm asking you,
不是因为我是警察
not because I'm a cop,
而是因为我不想失去他
but because I don't want to lose him.
我爱他 求你了
I love him, please.
求你了
Please.
碧豆 求你了
Please Beetle.
警察 都别动
Police! Don't move!
他在哪? 他在哪?
Where is he? Where is he?
叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
猜你今天忙完得喝上一杯
Thought maybe you could use a drink after today.
谢谢
Thanks.
至少我们救了一个孩子的命
At least we saved that boy's life,
很了不起 不是吗?
that's something, right?
干杯
Cheers.
那么杰西卡丽  他们俩什么情况?
So Jesse and Khali, what's happening between those two?
只不过是卡丽在劝说嫌犯
It was just Khali working the target.
不计代价
Whatever it took.
那就好
Good.
因为在同事恋情
'Cause relationships in the same unit,
不会有好结果
they never work.
不会吗
No.
不会
你知道你今天救了我的命 我想
You know, you saved my life today, I think.
没错
That's right.
你欠我好大一个人情
You owe me big time.
所以
So...
我那时说的是真的吗?
Did I mean everything that I said?
是的
Yeah.
还是就是为了劝说碧豆?
Or was it just a way to talk down Beetle?
你知道我喜欢你
You know that I like you.
你知道
You know...
我们不能继续这样 对吧?
we gotta stop this, right?
我们会的
And we will.